**MENU**

CLOSE

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Intimate Merger, Inc. (the “Company”) recognizes the importance of your personal information obtained through its businesses, considers the protection of your personal information as a social obligation, complies with applicable laws and ordinances, and is committed to handle it properly. The Company’s head office is located at 3-5-27 Roppongi, Minato-ku, Tokyo, Japan. The Company act as a Data Controller.

1\. Basic Principles regarding Protection of Personal Information

Both the Company’s executives and employees endeavor to protect and handle your personal information properly, make the utmost efforts to secure against unauthorized access, loss or leakage of personal information, and strive to manage such information securely.

2\. Obtaining Personal Information

The Company does not collect or use your personal information without your consent. Even when the Company asks you for your consent, it specifies the purpose(s) and scope of use in advance and uses only to the extent of your consent. Furthermore, when acquiring data including your personal information from third parties, the Company makes proper contracts with them to protect your personal information.

The items and purposes of use of personal information acquired by the Company are as follows.

| Classification | Item | Purpose of use |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Name of persons in charge of client company, mass media company, and company with whom we interact in connection with the Company's business.  <br>Name of persons who have exchanged business cards with the Company. | To hold an event for which you have applied and to contact you regarding it.  <br>To analyze in order to improve services. (e.g., surveys) (If any rule of the handling of personal information is separately stipulated for the surveys, etc., that rule will prevail.)  <br>To notify and contact regarding products and services.  <br>To respond to inquiries, requests, complaints, etc. |
| Address | Address of persons who have exchanged business cards with the Company. | To notify and contact regarding products and services.  <br>To notify and contact regarding events. |
| Online Identifiers | CookieID, DeviceID , IP address | To implement operations such as marketing measures and personalization (providing information based on personal attributes and behavior history) as commissioned work.  <br>To verify and improve advertising effectiveness, to create reports regarding it, and to report to clients.  <br>To aggregate user attributes as statistical information to the extent that they cannot be identified as individuals, and to use it as reference material for analyzing the usage status of the Company's service and improving it.  <br>To optimize advertisement distribution through the Company's services.  <br>To develop, improve, and increase convenience of new products and services. |
| Geolocation data | Data that identifies a location when combined with IP address such as data that identifies the city location. | To use online identifiers and to utilize location-related information in advertisement delivery, etc., as a consignment business, to the extent that it does not identify an individual. |
| Activity on Internet or other similar network | URL, referrer (the URL of the website you accessed just before the website you are currently browsing, title, meta keyword (collection of information related to the web page you are viewing), information about activity history (clicks on delivered advertisements, purchase history, etc.) of the visited website page. | Same purpose as Online identifier. |

3\. Use of Personal Information

The Company uses your personal information only within the scope of purpose of use and to the extent necessary for our services. When the Company use your personal information for any purposes for which you have not given consent, it obtains your consent for such purposes in advance.

4\. Security Control Measures

The Company safeguards your personal information under the strict control. It appoints a manager responsible for the protection of your personal information and manages it properly.  
The Company retains your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purpose of use related to such information. In accordance with laws and regulations and the operational policy established by the Company, the Company will promptly delete your personal information when it is no longer necessary to retain such information, such as when the purpose of use related to the personal information is achieved.  
The Company retains information about activity history for up to two years from the date of your last visit to the website using the Company's service.

5\. Subcontracting the Processing of Personal Information

When the Company subcontracts the processing of your personal information to third parties, it does so only with your consent and the adequate supervision to the third parties.

6\. Disclosure of and Inquiry about Personal Information

If you have any request or inquiry about notification of the purpose of the use, disclosure, correction or deletion of the content, suspension of the use, etc. of your personal information, please contact the inquiry desk below. The inquiry desk will inform you about the procedure and the fee. When contacted, the inquiry desk will confirm your identity or your agent's authority. Foreign users may be able to exercise their right to request from the Company access to and rectification or erasure of personal information or restriction of processing concerning them or to object to processing as well as the right to data portability, and their right to withdraw their consent to the Company, to the extent permitted by the laws of their home country.

[Click here](https://intimatemerger.com/r/privacy-inquiry-en) for inquiries from overseas.

7\. Compliance

The Company complies with applicable laws and standards regarding personal information. If you believe that the Company has infringed your statutory rights, you may be able to lodge a complaint with your national data protection authority or other competent supervisory authority.

8\. Continuous Improvement of this Privacy Policy

The Company makes a continuous effort to enhance its internal system for handling the collected information by updating this privacy policy in response to changes of social demands.

9\. Opt-out

If you would like to opt-out of our services or review our FAQs, please refer to our opt-out page .

For the information about the privacy policy and the opt-out of behavioral targeting advertisement of the companies cooperating in the Company’s service, please visit the following links.

10\. Information Collected by the Company using Cookies

When providing its services, the Company assigns a random ID comprised of a string of characters (“Unique ID”) to each browser used by a user and saves it in the cookie of that browser in order to distinguish users. Also the Company collects the following data (collectively referred as “Behavior Data”. Unique ID and Behavior Data are collectively referred as “Behavior Information”), through its services.

* Behavior history and attributes of a user in the website that is using the Company's services ("Website")
* Attributes of a user to which the advertisement is served with the Company's services

More specifically, the Company collects the following Behavior Information. Unique ID is randomly assigned to each browser, meaning that the following information is never combined with data which can identify an individual.

* Unique ID saved in the cookie
* Date and time the user visits the Website or the advertisement is served to the user
* URL of the Website the user visits
* Title and meta keywords of the Website the user visits
* Referrer of the user's visit to the Website
* Client IP address
* User agent of the browser
* Language and encoding settings of the browser
* Screen size and color depth of the browser

The information collected by the Company is used for the following purposes.

* Market analysis and marketing
* Inferring attribute information such as gender, interests and preferences
* Behavioral targeting advertisement
* Supervision of unauthorized actions
* Provision to third parties (as electronic data) in order to achieve the purposes of 1 to 4 above

In addition, the items of information corresponding to personal information and the purpose of use are as described in "2. Obtaining Personal Information ".

Privacy Policy for U.S. Residents

The following policy applies to the personal information of residents of U.S., superseding the above policy. However, the above policy shall still apply with respect to matters not specified in the following policy.

1\. Items of Personal Information Collected by the Company.

The Company have collected the following personal information in the past 12 months for business and commercial purposes.

| Category | Item | Purpose of collecting |
| --- | --- | --- |
| A. Identifiers | CookieID, DeviceID, IP-address | To implement operations such as marketing measures and personalization (providing information based on personal attributes and behavior history) as commissioned work.  <br>To verify and improve advertising effectiveness, to create reports regarding it, and report to clients.  <br>To aggregate user attributes as statistical information to the extent that they cannot be identified as individuals, and to use it as reference material for analyzing the usage status of the Company's service and improving it.  <br>To optimize advertisement distribution through the Company's services.  <br>To develop, improve, and increase convenience of new products and services. |
| B. Commercial information | History of web pages you have visited, record of your purchase | To implement customer classification, customer analysis, and consumer trend research to perform commissioned work, in addition to the same purpose as A (Identifiers). |
| C. Internet or other similar network activity information | URL, referrer (the URL of the website you accessed just before the website you are currently browsing),title, meta keyword（collection of information related to the web page you are viewing), information about activity history (clicks on delivered advertisements, etc.） | Same purpose as A (Identifiers) |
| D. Geolocation data | Data that identifies a location when combined with IP address such as data that identifies the city location | To utilize location-related information in commissioned word such as advertisement delivery and data analysis, to the extent that it does not identify an individual, in addition to the same purpose as A (Identifiers) |
| E. Inferences drawn from other personal information | Advertising segment, Data of interests (Segment information related to inference for advertisement distribution that matches the interests and attributes (estimated gender and age) of Internet users) | Same purpose as A (Identifiers) |

The Company have collected personal information listed above from the Company's partner SSP and media company.

2\. Purpose for disclosing Personal Information

The Company may share the personal information the Company collect for the following purposes:

* To disclose to our subsidiaries and affiliates for purposes necessary for our service
* To transfer to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, spin-off, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets
* To respond to requests by law enforcement or requests by law, court order or governmental regulation
* To achieve the purpose for which the user provided personal information

3\. Share of Personal Information

The Company may share your personal information to the following categories of third parties.

Service providers:

* Client
* Agency
* Ad technology service provider（Vendor）
* Publisher
* Other marketing tool operating companies

4\. Sales and Disclose of Personal Information in the preceding 12 months

In the preceding 12 months, the Company has not sold personal information, and has not disclosed personal information for a business purpose.

5\. Notice about Rights of U.S. Residents

Users have the rights of following a through g under the CCPA;

**a. Right to know about personal information collected, disclosed, or sold**

You have the right to request that the Company disclose the following information in the past 12 months from the time of your request.

* The categories of personal information the Company has collected about you.
* The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected.
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information.
* The categories of third parties with whom the Company sells or shares personal information.
* The specific pieces of personal information the Company has collected about you.
* The categories of personal information that the Company sold or shared about you and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold.

**b. Right to Access and Portability**

Users have the right to access information guaranteed by the CCPA, the Company must provide electronic media, available and accessible format.

**c. Right to request deletion of personal information**

You have the right to request that the Company delete any of your personal information which the Company has collected.

**d. Right to request correction of personal information**

You have the right to request that the Company correct inaccurate personal information about you which the Company has collected.

**e. Right to opt-out of sharing of personal information**

For questions about opting out of personal information for US residents, please [click here](https://intimatemerger.com/r/privacy-inquiry-en).  
Please [click here](https://intimatemerger.com/r/do-not-share) for “Do not share my personal information”.

**f. Users under the age of 16**

The Company does not have actual knowledge that it sells the personal information of users under 16 years of age. If we have actual knowledge that a user is less than 16 years of age, it will not sell personal information of the user unless the Company obtain the affirmative authorization of the user or the user's parent or guardian, depending on the user's age.

**g. Right to non-discrimination**

You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment as the following for the exercise of your rights conferred by the CCPA:

* Deny you goods or services.
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

6\. Requests through duly authorized agent

You may also make the above requests through a duly authorized agent.

7\. Contact

If you have any requests specified in the CCPA (request for disclosure, access and portability rights, corrections, deletions, etc.), or any other questions, please [click here](https://intimatemerger.com/r/privacy-inquiry-en).

Appendix

**Inquiries**

Please [click here](https://intimatemerger.com/r/privacy-inquiry-en) for any inquiries in relation to the contents of this privacy policy.

**Last updated**

October 3, 2023

運営メディア

© Intimate Merger, Inc.
